ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL
HIDDEN LOVE BY ZHU YI
I don't usually drink much.
-So--
-Who did you go with?
My roommates.
They were all people I know.
Roommates?
What about the guy who came out
with you yesterday?
The one who is 195 cm tall
and just gave you a hamburger.
Is he also your roommate?
No, that is my roommate's
boyfriend's friend.
Is that him?
What do you mean?
The guy you like.
Is it him?
Is he?
No.
No?
So tell me.
If that isn't your type, what is?
I don't want to.
Jiaxu.
-The bubble--
-Is it a guy who is cute
and delicate-looking?
No.
He…
He's manly.
Manly?
So…
You like
muscular guys.
Is that it?
No.
No muscles but is manly.
Also, he's nice to everyone.
But the guy you described
sounds like a jerk.
He's not a jerk.
-He is.
-He isn't.
You're so nosy.
I'm nosy?
I've never met a guy like that in my life.
-Gosh.
-I'm just curious.
You're so nosy.
Can you stop asking?
Fine.
I won't ask anymore.
If you're curious,
just look in the mirror.
Jiaxu.
Yes?
You…
You're in your twenties now.
Why don't you get a girlfriend
instead of bothering me--
Where would I get a girlfriend?
Why don't you
introduce one to me?
That won't do.
I only know girls around my age.
Around your age?
I'm fine with that.
What do you mean?
The literal meaning.
Is he teasing me?
He has never said
something like this to me before.
Pull over.
Mom!
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi!
I've missed you so much.
You're finally home.
What took so long? Was the flight delayed?
No.
It was Sang Yan.
Sang Yan made me wait
at the airport for so long.
Why?
Why did you make Zhizhi wait?
No, Mom. You told me to buy
her favorite crispy taro-crusted duck.
-Yes.
-I was in line for half an hour.
You should've gone earlier.
-That's right.
-You made her wait alone.
That was so dangerous.
My sweetheart. You've lost weight.
I haven't.
I made your favorite dish. What is it?
-Steamed fish.
-Not only that.
-I bought strawberries.
-Strawberries?
Big strawberries!
-White strawberries.
-Bring the luggage in.
-I…
-Bring it all in.
When the little princess comes home,
I'm just a helper.
The door!
The little princess is home.
Mom.
Your New Year's gift.
You bought it for me?
You'll like it. Open it.
Careful, this is hot.
Is this it?
Yes.
And this too.
You bought two.
I saved up for a long while.
Thank you so much.
Dad, this is your New Year's gift.
-Thank you.
-It's hand cream.
Use it when you go to construction sites.
Then your hands
won't get chapped during winter.
Thank you, Zhizhi.
-Good girl.
-She is so considerate.
-I've grown up.
-Only she would think of this.
I've become mature.
Thank you.
Don't worry about me.
-Don't worry.
-You give her too much allowance.
Stop funding her next semester.
Where is mine?
That's more like it.
It looks great.
-Really?
-Super cool.
Mom, look at him.
Isn't it?
-What's wrong?
-What is this? I don't want it. Take it.
Why not?
-It looks ugly.
-It's not.
I don't like it!
Dad, does this look good to you?
It's stupid.
It's nice.
I know you have a fine taste.
Asymmetric glasses are trendy this year.
-Don't you like it?
-No, I don't.
-No?
-No.
-No!
Say you like it!
I like it!
Say you like it wholeheartedly.
I wholeheartedly don't like it!
-Then don't wear it.
-That's enough. I love this liveliness.
Eat this.
-Sit.
-Doesn't it taste good?
Little demon.
Let me tell you.
I waited in line for half an hour
to buy this crispy taro-crusted duck.
You had better eat it and…
Thank you, Sang Yan.
Give my glasses back to me.
I'll take them since they're free.
Does it taste good?
Zhizhi.
Last time, you told me
that Xiaoduan had appendicitis.
How is he now?
He has recovered well.
The doctor said it was caused
by irregular meal timings.
He didn't eat properly.
So you heard that too.
You mustn't skip meals.
He had a tough life before.
He was often working.
That probably impacted his health.
How is he doing at work now?
Pretty well.
Many of my classmates know
about the game he designed.
It's very popular.
That's good to hear.
The boy is pretty good.
Look at Sang Yan. He looks dumb.
Listen, Sang Yan.
Look at Xiaoduan,
then look at yourself.
I set up a meeting for you
and Mrs. Zhang's daughter.
She waited for you all afternoon
and you didn't show up.
I told you.
I wouldn't go.
I set it up for you. Why didn't you go?
You should've turned up out of courtesy
and met with her.
Dad, Mom.
Do I look like I need that?
Absolutely not.
So stop setting up meetings.
I won't go.
Was it a blind date?
Fine.
I've poked my meddling nose.
You're always doing nothing all day.
I thought you would have time for tea.
I didn't know you were so busy.
That was close.
You're so stubborn.
You'll end up old and alone.
Enough. Don't waste the strawberries.
I find that we've lost our dynamic.
I'll toss one. Open wide.
Don't waste the strawberries.
-Zhizhi, this steamed fish is for you.
-I'll toss the bowl.
Zhizhi, I made this steamed fish for you.
Hurry and eat.
Come on. It will get cold.
-Okay.
-Hurry and eat.
Come on.
I don't need this. Put it back.
I don't need this!
Are you trying to kill me?
Put it away.
What's wrong with you?
You must want something.
Are you going on blind dates?
Why do you care?
No wonder you're suddenly so kind to me.
So did you not go on that blind date?
Do you think I need to go on a blind date?
Don't you need to?
What will you do
with the rest of your life
if you don't go on blind dates?
Was it because you felt embarrassed to go?
If you do feel that way,
you can
ask Duan Jiaxu to go with you.
Take him with you.
You're single.
He's one year older than you
and he's single too.
Besides…
Besides, I think he may
want a girlfriend now.
Maybe you can go to him in Yihe.
Or he can come to you in Nanwu.
You two can go together.
Then you won't feel embarrassed.
Why?
Did Duan Jiaxu get on your wrong side?
I just think
that he's not young anymore.
If he doesn't find a girlfriend, he might
end up being pathetically alone.
If he ends up pathetically alone,
that's his business.
Don't compare me with him.
So are you going on blind dates or not?
I don't need to.
In that case…
But Mom told you to go.
Do you know why?
Because there's a girl
trying to pursue me right now.
Got it?
What's with that look? I mean it.
So…
You can tell Duan Jiaxu
to go alone
and enjoy the blind date
with his tacky pickup lines.
Open the gate.
Open it.
Climb over it.
Open the gate! You're so childish!
Call me handsome. Come on.
Do it.
You're handsome.
Louder.
Even louder.
What's wrong with you?
You're handsome. Open the gate now.
That's the way.
You're a good sister.
Please.
Handsome, my foot.
Hey!
I have to go out later.
Mom!
Zhizhi, smell this.
Does it smell like the sun?
Why would it smell like the sun?
I've sunned the quilt all day.
That's why I'm just making the bed now.
All right.
Go and get the teddy bear blanket.
Is it still in the cabinet?
Yes, it's in there.
Okay.
-Found it?
-Yes.
- I'll put it here.
-I'll do it.
Mom, go and get some rest.
It's late now.
-Good night.
All right. I'll go and wash this first.
-Go ahead.
-Okay. Good night.
-Bye.
SANG ZHI, HAPPY 18TH BIRTHDAY
Where would I get a girlfriend?
Why don't you
introduce one to me?
That won't do.
I only know girls around my age.
Around your age?
I'm fine with that.
Is he serious about that?
SANG ZHI
Jiaxu.
I think Sang Yan has a girlfriend.
Really?
BROTHER NO. 2
I think she's a younger girl.
SANG ZHI
Don't tell me he likes a minor.
Is it fine as long as she's an adult?
An adult would be in college.
Doesn't that make her a grown-up?
So why not?
She's only asking about Sang Yan, right?
It's acceptable when it happens
to someone else.
But if it were to happen to herself,
she would probably find it hard to accept.
After all, to her,
I'm just a big brother.
Had we not met each other until now,
I at 19 and he at 24,
he would've seen me as a peer.
Sadly, that didn't happen.
Perhaps in his eyes,
I will always be a 14-year-old girl
who is just his good friend's sister.
DON'T TELL ME HE LIKES A MINOR.
IS IT FINE AS LONG AS SHE'S AN ADULT?
CHAPTER 13, FEEL YOU OUT
I'M GUESSING YOU'RE FALLING TOO
I've been busy planning my wedding
and also had to come to Yihe for work.
If you hadn't called me,
I wouldn't have had much to eat today.
Then eat more.
Order more if you want.
I won't hold back with you.
Listen, Duan Jiaxu.
I won't ask you and Sang Yan
to be my groomsmen.
Why? Do you have a problem with me?
I have a problem with you and Sang Yan.
Picture my wedding.
If you, Sang Yan, and I
are standing together,
people might think
you're there to steal my bride.
That's nonsensical.
Duan Jiaxu.
We haven't talked much
on the phone lately.
Why haven't you contacted me?
What has been keeping you busy?
What else but work?
You haven't mentioned
the girl you like lately.
Let's talk about it.
Nothing has happened.
There isn't much to talk about.
Don't keep mum. Tell me. I'm so curious.
Please. What kind of girl is she?
She's a young lady.
She's a bit younger.
You don't know her.
What's wrong with being young
so long as she isn't a minor?
Pursue her if she's of legal age
or I'll look down on you.
It's not like that.
I feel somewhat guilty about it.
Guilty? Aren't you worried
that she'll get taken?
That's normal.
If she meets a good guy,
I'll be happy for her.
Does that mean
she has someone she likes?
This girl is impressive
to take no interest in you.
Duan Jiaxu, don't be sad.
What kind of guy does she like?
I'll analyze it and give you advice.
Tell me.
Well, this guy
is quite a flirt.
He is a ladies' man and nice to everyone.
He might even be a bit shameless.
Isn't that you?
Are you insulting me?
No.
Is there any chance
that she's talking about you?
Impossible.
I've met that guy before.
His image fits her description quite well.
He's quite flirty.
He's just a jerk.
Maybe not.
You see, one speaks contrary to their mind
in front of their crush.
When I was in college, I chased a girl,
Wan Ling in Foreign Languages.
I was her rebound when she had a breakup.
When they got back together, she told me,
"Qian Fei, what kind of girl do you like?
I can introduce one to you."
What could I say to her?
I simply made up someone based on her.
You made up a girl based on her?
It's not very likely.
But it's possible.
Right?
Listen, I swear to you.
I haven't met many guys who fit
that description better than you do.
Miss, I want to order more!
Am I the guy she likes?
Sir, what would you like to order?
-Chicken wings.
-All right.
-And this too.
-Okay, right away.
I've arrived in Nanwu.
See you later.
Okay.
Why did he tell me this?
-Do I leave the red packet here?
-No need.
They're waiting. Hurry over.
-No?
-It's fine.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
What took you so long today?
The traffic was terrible.
Listen, Qian Fei is really nervous.
Buddy!
Did you put on weight?
-A little.
-Not much.
Good, you're happy.
-Hi, Sang Zhi.
-Qian Fei.
Congratulations.
I stopped her
from giving a red packet at the door.
-You won't accept it, right?
-Right.
It's just a little something. Accept it.
I can't. It's the thought that counts.
No need for this.
Please take it.
No.
You're so generous today.
Am I? I expect two packets from you.
Don't just drink by yourself.
You and I are drinking
after the wedding, all right?
-Take your seats.
-Right, come on.
-You'll sit here.
-Sit here.
Let's go, Sang Zhi.
-Sit.
-Look after them.
-You sit here.
-Sit.
If he doesn't want it, give it to me.
Jiaxu!
-Jiaxu, over here!
-Over here.
What took you so long?
I was going in circles outside.
You cleaned up nicely today.
He's handsome, right?
Hey, man. Do you know what time it is now?
You nearly missed my wedding.
I was going in circles.
-Okay, I'll go and get ready.
-Isn't that the tie I gave him?
Do your best.
-I'll get ready now.
-Go ahead.
-Sit there.
-Leave it to me.
-Come on, take a seat.
-Sit.
You're so well-dressed today.
Jiaxu, say something nice.
I'll give you a red packet for New Year.
It's hard to say something nice about you.
Why don't I call you "darling brother"?
Call me "brother."
I'm fine with "brother."
Darling brother.
Is he drunk already?
Who are you trying to gross out?
Jiaxu, you two have become grosser
since university.
Indeed.
Darling brother, they're badmouthing me.
Gross!
This is mine now.
Starting today,
Sang Yan is my darling brother.
Are you insane?
Sang Yan, give in. It's okay.
Sure, okay.
It makes me cringe.
I've got goosebumps all over.
-Let's drink.
-Bottoms up.
Brother.
Don't call me that.
Hearing that makes me sick now.
Then…
What?
Did something happen
to him?
He seems weird today.
I'll tell you what happened to him.
Here.
Yihe Psychiatric Hospital.
Go straight there when you get back.
Darling brother, you're so considerate
to find a hospital for me.
Man, stop calling me that. Okay?
Why, my darling brother?
Scoot over, Sang Zhi. Let's switch seats.
I'm going to puke even before I drink.
Sit over there.
Okay? Please, I beg of you.
What's wrong with you?
Scoot over.
-It has been a while!
-Maybe for you two.
We just met up last week!
-Next, let's welcome our groom,
-What should I say?
who's plump from love's nourishment,
but still looks handsome,
Qian Fei,
and his beloved bride, Shiwen!
Let's welcome them to the stage!
I wonder if the staircase
can bear the weight of their love!
Let's give them a round of applause!
Come on, Feifei.
Look at this sturdy staircase.
It's like the path of their future.
With each and every step they take,
they walk their way to their happiness
and stability.
And this moment
deserves cheering and applause
from all of you!
Qian Fei.
You have grown so chubby from love.
I know
you must have much gratitude deep within.
Why not take the mic
and say something to everyone?
I…
First of all, thank you
for coming to my wedding.
I never thought
that I would get married so soon.
I…
I'm sure my buddies didn't expect
that I would get married so soon either.
I also want to thank my wife.
My figure and height
aren't a problem for her.
Even someone like me
can marry such a beautiful wife.
I…
Guys, I've got a wife!
Well done!
Help me take a photo.
All guests,
let's raise our glasses!
What are you doing?
Raise your glasses.
Yes, right! Raise our glasses.
Buddies!
Eat and drink your fill!
Cheers!
-All right!
-Cheers!
Let's count down from three
and wish them a happy marriage!
Three, two, one!
-Have a happy marriage!
Cheers!
Okay, as we watch the lovely newlyweds
leave the wedding stage,
this marks the start
of Qian Fei and Shiwen's wedding banquet!
-Come on.
-May all of you eat up
-Let's dig in.
-and become as chubby as Qian Fei!
I want this one.
It's so close to you.
Fine.
You can have
all the corn.
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY HI?
Are you happy now?
I can't take it anymore.
BROTHER NO. 2
Why didn't you say hi?
Zhizhi,
I bought you a chocolate cake.
It's in the fridge.
Remember to eat it.
It's not important.
Who is Zhizhi?
Like you don't know.
It's my nickname.
Why doesn't your brother call you that?
He calls me that occasionally.
When I don't tick him off.
Who else calls you that?
My dad, mom, aunt, uncle,
and eldest aunt.
Those who are close to me call me that.
And what's up with "Brother No. 2"?
Brother No. 1 and Brother No. 2.
Is there a problem with that?
Why am I your Brother No. 2?
You're older than Sang Yan.
So
one and two.
Fine.
How old is the guy you like?
Why is he bringing this up again?
Why do you care?
Tell me.
Is he in the same year
and same school as you?
No.
Who else do you know?
I know people outside of school too.
How did you meet him?
We met while we hung out.
Where?
A bar.
That's not right.
When you were drunk, you told me
that you met him at a KTV.
Did I say that?
What did I say?
Yes.
We met at a KTV.
I've met a lot of people,
so I got confused.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just think
that Qian Fei is quite smart.
What does Qian Fei have to do with this?
How did you fall for him?
Give me a break, please.
Why should I tell you?
-Look at him.
-Let's switch seats.
No, I don't want to.
-You…
-Sit over here.
Just sit there.
My darling brother, eat up. Have more.
No way.
You just sit there.
WE'VE TIED THE KNOT,
A HAPPY AND LASTING MARRIAGE
Top it off.
What does this mean?
Are you not drinking?
Is this how you respond
to your challenge five years ago?
Let me have a bite. Quickly.
I'm starving.
Here.
-I'm so hungry.
-Eat something.
-Then we'll drink after this.
-All right.
Okay, don't worry.
-No problem.
-You didn't even take a sip.
-I'll fill it up for you.
-Okay.
Where is Qian Fei?
He's seeing the guests off.
They're such a sweet couple.
My goodness. I envy him so much.
Envious?
Lift your head. What's wrong?
When are you leaving?
I haven't seen them in a long time.
-I want to drink with them.
-Okay.
Here. Let's drink until we drop.
Sang Yan, give up.
I'm heading home then.
Sure. Go home first. Do you need a ride?
No, I can go by myself.
I really can't stand those two.
-Good idea.
-Okay.
Come on, guys.
Let's drink.
Jiaxu, I'm heading home first.
Here, a toast to you.
I'm leaving, everyone.
-Goodbye.
-Bye, little demon.
Be careful.
Little demon.
Bye.
Don't drink too much.
Don't worry. I'll take care of him.
There he goes again.
Sang Zhi.
Why are you walking so fast?
Are you leaving too?
No.
But it's late now.
I'll drive you home in your brother's car.
Didn't you drink…
You were sitting next to me all night.
Don't you know if I drank or not?
I know you didn't.
But you don't have to see me home.
I can go back by myself.
Driving back and forth is troublesome.
Not at all.
It might be troublesome
if it were someone else.
What? Are you giving it back to me?
I'm returning the red packet
to our Zhizhi.
Wait.
What did you just call me?
Zhizhi.
You said people close to you
call you that.
You should keep this.
Since you've called Sang Yan…
You should get something for that.
It's for Zhizhi.
It's no loss.
Take it.
Let's go.
When are you returning to school?
Tomorrow morning.
What time?
The flight is just after 8:00 a.m.
We're on the same flight.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll come and take you to the airport.
Thank you, Jiaxu.
I'll go inside then.
It's your New Year's gift.
Thank you, Jiaxu.
Open it.
Are these my initials?
Do you like it?
Well…
Go in and sleep soon.
All right.
Good night, Jiaxu.
Good night.
A bracelet with my initials on it.
What does that mean?
What does a bracelet mean as a gift?
"BRACELET" SOUNDS LIKE
"CHERISHED LOVE"
IT'S A GIFT FOR LOVERS
Love?
FRUIT FARM
How much is this?
Please scan here.
Okay.
It's done.
Is it for me?
You seem to like eating this.
Let's go.
Are you not eating it?
Do you want one?
I'll try it.
Come closer.
What?
Do you want me to feed you?
Sang Zhi.
Watch yourself.
Don't take advantage of me.
You're shameless.
UNKNOWN ARTIST - CAR MUSIC 6
VOLUME